# CAMILA APARICIO

# FRONT END WEB DEVELOPER



(647) 975-7248



camilaaparicioo@hotmail.com



linkedin.com/in/camilaaparicio



www.camilaaparicio.com



Toronto, Ontario

## **ABOUT ME**

I am a front-end developer building engaging, accessible, and responsive websites. My diverse background has taught me how to be a strong team member in a variety of high performing groups and exposed me to experiences requiring logical problem solving. I have also been able to develop strong soft skills, such as effective communication and a strong work ethic allowing web development to be the perfect field for my skills.

Languages: English & Spanish

# **SKILLS**



HTML



**Command Line** 



CJJ



Git / GitHub



Sass



**REST APIs** 



**JavaScript** 



**Firebase** 



JQuery



Web Accessibility



React



Responsive Web Design

# **EDUCATION**

# Juno College of Technology

- Immersive Web Development Certificate
- Intro To Java Script
- Intro to Web Development

# **University of Guelph-Humber**

 Honours Bachelor of Applied Science in Social Work | 2012-2016

## **PROJECTS**



### **Movie Searcher**

- HTML, CSS, Vanilla JavaScript, REST API, Pair Programming.
- Allows for users to search up movies through the IMDB API.
- Pair Programming collaborative project.



## Meme in a Giffy

- HTML, CSS, React, Firebase, Rest API, Group Programing.
- Allows user to generate their own memes by inputting text & memes are saved in Firebase database.
- Group Programming collaborative project.



#### **E-commerce Store**

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, REACT, Rest API.
- An e-commerce store that provide categories for items, and functioning cart.

### **EXPERIENCE**

#### Pension Technician

Morneau Shepell - Feb 2019 - Sept 2021

- Calculated and issued benefit payments in accordance with plan rules and legislation.
- Answered queries from clients, plan members and trustees, providing relevant information and appropriate follow-up.

#### **Administrative Assistant**

First Republic Capital - Jan 2018 - Feb 2019

 Liaised with internal and external parties involved with the proceedings in preparation of private placements.

#### **Front Desk Coordinator**

Cactus Club Café - Jan 2016 - Dec 2017

 Coordinated and managed front desk team through effective guidance and strong communication skills in a professional manner in a high volume and demanding environment.

#### **Toronto Rape Crisis Center**

Program Assistant - 2015- 2016

- Collaborated on a team for the start-up and planning of a Latin American Women's Program, assisted with administrative tasks, research and event planning.
- Responded to crisis calls & provided individuals with accesible information.